wabafun.com 2005-03-05

# Superstructs | WABA Fun, LLC Privacy Policy

**Superstructs Characters**  
Included with Every Set  |   
| **Privacy Policy**  
---  
WABA Fun, LLC will not share your information with any third party company, including email marketing firms. Your personal information will be kept secure and confidential in our database purely for our own marketing purposes. If you wish to be excluded from occasional emailings from WABA Fun (the company that sells Superstructs), please send us a note to [info@wabafun.com](mailto:info@wabafun.com). Thank you! 

**How WABA Fun Collects and Uses Personal Information**

The specific information collected is as follows: 

  * Your name
  * An address
  * Your email and daytime phone number

**Links**  
When you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to third-party websites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies. WABA Fun does not recommend or endorse any products, services, materials or the privacy policies suggested by those websites. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, WABA Fun cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any website. **Surveys**  
In the future, the Superstructs website may request information from users via surveys. Participation in those surveys is voluntary and the user has a choice to disclose or not disclose information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code, personal preferences, etc.). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and effectiveness of the site. **Receiving Email**  
Email is occasionally sent from WABA Fun regarding certain promotional merchandise opportunities. **Customer Service Inquiries**  
WABA Fun uses return email addresses and phone support to answer the inquires sent to the WABA Fun Customer Service department. The phone support number can be found on the Superstructs website. **Does Superstructs.com use 'Cookies' on the site?**  
WABA Fun, like virtually all e-commerce sites today, occasionally issues 'cookies' to create a more effective and convenient site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user for a particular website. WABA Fun does not store any sensitive information in the cookie, but the cookie can be used to allow WABA Fun to offer unique functionality on the site. WABA Fun also stores your name in a cookie file, so WABA Fun can give you a personal greeting when you come back to the website.
